{
  "subject": "mathematics",
  "grade": "kindergarten",
  "question_count": 150,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5924",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 + 16?",
      "answer": "30",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 30
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3823",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 5?",
      "answer": "17",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 17
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1780",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 + 20?",
      "answer": "38",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 38
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_9873",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 12?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1682",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 + 17?",
      "answer": "35",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 35
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4853",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 11?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5985",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 2?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8050",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 9?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6951",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 + 18?",
      "answer": "31",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 18,
        "result": 31
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8736",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 6?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4127",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 8?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_9333",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 12?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4445",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 7?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5397",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 4?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6540",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 11?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3861",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 6?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1535",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 16?",
      "answer": "23",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5362",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 - 2?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8730",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 9?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4049",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 + 13?",
      "answer": "19",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 13,
        "result": 19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1026",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 - 10?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2697",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 6?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5707",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 4?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7593",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 + 20?",
      "answer": "28",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7714",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 16?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_9394",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 1?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3409",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 6?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1985",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 - 1?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1507",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 6?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1749",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 20?",
      "answer": "37",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 37
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3330",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 2?",
      "answer": "17",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 17
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6570",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 + 13?",
      "answer": "31",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 13,
        "result": 31
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3514",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 + 18?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 18,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3527",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 + 20?",
      "answer": "34",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 34
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4610",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 19?",
      "answer": "23",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2785",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 - 8?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8131",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 + 19?",
      "answer": "33",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 33
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3015",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 7?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2978",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 12?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6573",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 3?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1192",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 + 7?",
      "answer": "23",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4728",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 + 19?",
      "answer": "38",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 38
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1334",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 12?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1368",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 1?",
      "answer": "13",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5449",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 7?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1312",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 + 5?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1399",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 - 3?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8997",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 12?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_9497",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 + 5?",
      "answer": "21",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8404",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 7?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2902",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 2?",
      "answer": "13",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4288",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 - 7?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5120",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 - 5?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7673",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 8?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3940",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 - 5?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7280",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 11?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4103",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 6?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3560",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 - 6?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6903",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 1?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7803",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 10?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1090",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 + 15?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7630",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 10?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5031",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 17?",
      "answer": "29",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 29
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4116",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 9?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5830",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 - 7?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6009",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 6?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7997",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 + 5?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2406",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 9?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5729",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 - 3?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4255",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 15?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6339",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 9?",
      "answer": "21",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1121",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 - 1?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1404",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 + 17?",
      "answer": "19",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5697",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 - 9?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1599",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 - 9?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4887",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 5?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2475",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 + 16?",
      "answer": "17",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 17
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4351",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 - 4?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3131",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 - 4?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3787",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 + 11?",
      "answer": "24",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6880",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 + 17?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4911",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 1?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7509",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 + 19?",
      "answer": "34",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 34
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7079",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 - 3?",
      "answer": "0",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4399",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 + 5?",
      "answer": "24",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1185",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 12?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3197",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 12?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4431",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 + 19?",
      "answer": "38",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 38
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_9541",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 11?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6307",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 9?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8211",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 7?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5462",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 4?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_9813",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 - 2?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2194",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 + 4?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7922",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 + 8?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1133",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 8?",
      "answer": "25",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 25
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6210",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 16?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3688",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 + 6?",
      "answer": "24",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1668",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 - 2?",
      "answer": "0",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3919",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 + 11?",
      "answer": "26",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 26
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4710",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 10?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2384",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 15?",
      "answer": "19",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7414",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 6?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5689",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 6?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5519",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 8?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6273",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 16?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8445",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 - 6?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7457",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 - 4?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3640",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 13?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 13,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2937",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 17?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4629",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 15?",
      "answer": "19",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1156",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 16?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2868",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 9?",
      "answer": "19",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5110",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 + 17?",
      "answer": "33",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 33
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5320",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 14?",
      "answer": "26",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 14,
        "result": 26
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6839",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 4?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3320",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 + 10?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6219",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 20?",
      "answer": "32",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 32
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8033",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 14?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 14,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6280",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 5 + 4?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 5,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5928",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 1?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4472",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 + 3?",
      "answer": "21",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2867",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 + 1?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4958",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 + 4?",
      "answer": "23",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4096",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 - 2?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6956",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 14?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 14,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5192",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 2?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7518",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 + 9?",
      "answer": "28",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1183",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 16?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5211",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 - 6?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6800",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 - 1?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7054",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 4?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7660",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 6?",
      "answer": "13",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8121",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 + 17?",
      "answer": "23",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7137",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 + 15?",
      "answer": "30",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 30
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8553",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 7?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_6667",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 16?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5673",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 9?",
      "answer": "13",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5776",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 9?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1465",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 5 + 7?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 5,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_7720",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 8?",
      "answer": "25",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 25
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2182",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 5?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_5702",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 10?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_8735",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 15?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4683",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 11?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_3320",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 3?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2733",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 9?",
      "answer": "21",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_2153",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 + 19?",
      "answer": "27",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 27
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_4744",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 + 15?",
      "answer": "30",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 30
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_0_1711",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "kindergarten",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 5 + 5?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 5,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 10
      }
    }
  ]
}